（上条(かみじょう)）
“吸血殺し(ディープブラッド)”こと 姫神秋沙(ひめがみ あいさ)を―
In order to save Himegami Aisa, also known as Deep Blood,
助けるべく わたくし上条当麻(とうま)と
その他１名のロン毛は―
I, Kamijyo Touma, and one other long-haired dude...
三沢塾(みさわじゅく)に殴り込みをかけたわけだが
...charged into Misawa Cram School.
What awaited us there was the alchemist, Aureolus Izzard,
and his counterattack that defied our imaginations.
そこで俺たちを待っていたのは―
錬金術師
アウレオルス＝イザードの―
想像を絶する返り討ち
Huh, wait!
…て ちょっと待て
What do you mean Index might have come here?
インデックスが来てるかも
しれねえって どういうことだ？
～♪
#09 Deep Blood
Vampire Killer
（上条）
ホントだな？
You sure?
（上条）
ホントに 野郎の居所を
つかんだんだな？
You really know where that guy's hiding, right?
（ステイル）
この僕が
ムダにビルの中を―
Did you think I'd ramble through this building for nothing?
散策していたとでも
思っているのかい？
それにしても―
But... to think that he could do anything he wants just by saying it...
言葉ひとつで 何でも
思いどおりにできちまうなんて
Damn it, how are we supposed to get back Himegami from him?
くそ！　あんな野郎から
どうやって姫神を…
And it seems like Index came here, too.
しかも インデックスのヤツまで
来てやがるみてえだし
Even if she did wander into here, he wouldn't attack her immediately like he did with us.
仮に
あの子が迷い込んでいたとしても
僕らみたいに いきなり
危害を加えられることはない
Because...
なぜならば… 待てよ
Wait!
（ぶつかる音）
アッ… 何だよ？
What?!
チッ… なるほど
Damn.
I see how it is!
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）そういうことか
（上条）うん？
３年も潜伏していれば
世情にも疎くなるというものだ
Hide yourself for three years, and you wouldn't know what's happening in the world.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
必然…
Inevitably, if no religion or technology can undo a wrong,
あらゆる信仰 技術をもってしても
正せぬ不当があるのなら―
人のことわりを外れることに
何のためらいがあろう
why would any hesitation be necessary in taking a stray path from human reasoning?
（姫神）
この人？
This person...
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
自然… やがて お前も
その悲しみから解き放たれる
Naturally, you will be released from that grief some day.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
もうまもなくだ
The time is near.
Quietly, attract them from the deep parts of the dark,
粛然　かかる漆黒のかなたから
呼び寄せるがいい
those vampires that fall for the smell of your sweet blood.
その甘美なる血の匂いによって
吸血鬼たちを
（姫神）
誰も傷つけずに済む　もう誰も
No one will need to be hurt.
No one, anymore.
（上条）姫神！
（姫神）ハッ…
Himegami!
あっ… インデックス！
Index!
Damn you!
くそ！　あっ…
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
残念だが 君に
目的を成し遂げることはできないよ
Unfortunately, I can't let you attain your objective.
フン…
今更ながら 我が真意に気づいたか
You noticed my true aim, albeit a bit late.
ならば その大成を前に―
Then before my great accomplishment...
おのが無力を嘆き
嫉妬に身を焦がすがよい
...you will lament your own lack of power...
...and scorch your bodies with jealousy.
Hey, it'll be worth the scorching if it works.
うまくいくなら
焦がしがいもあるんだがね
繰り返すが
君に彼女を救うことはできない
I repeat, you won't be able to save her... to save Index.
インデックスを救うことはね
インデックスを？
Save Index?
You simply failed at saving her.
貴様は
しくじったというだけのことだ
But I will save...
だが 私は…
私は この子を…
...this girl...
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
10万3,000冊もの魔道書を
一身に背負い
...who shoulders the burden of 103,000 grimoires...
決して その呪縛から
逃(のが)れることのできぬ少女
...and cannot escape from this curse...
にもかかわらず―
And regardless of this, she accepts her fate...
その運命を受け入れて なお―
...and wishes for the fortune of others more than worrying about her own misfortune.
おのが不幸より
他人の幸福のために…
This guy knew Index?
こいつ
インデックスを知っていた？
そう　彼もインデックスの
パートナーだったのさ
Yeah, he was one of Index's partners in the past.
（上条）えっ？
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）今年は君　去年は僕
This year, it's you.
Last year, it was me.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
そして
３年前のパートナーが この―
And her partner from three years ago
was this Aureolus Izzard.
アウレオルス＝イザードと
いうわけだ
これまで 禁書目録は―
To this day, Index-Librorum-Prohibitorum needs to have her memories erased every year or else she would die.
１年ごとに記憶を消さねば
生きていくことができなかった
これは必定であり 人の身には
あらがえぬ宿命　しかし…
This was a definite matter, a fate that people cannot defy.
However...
Conversely, it could be conquered if it weren't a human's body?
逆に言えば
人ならぬ身を使えば済む？
Vampires are those that possess immortal life.
吸血鬼とは 無限の命を持つもの
They possess the ability to save an infinite amount of memories in the same brain as humans.
無限の記憶を
人と同じ脳に蓄え続けるもの
あるのだよ 吸血鬼には
They have it, those vampires.
They have a method of not losing their "self" no matter how many memories they take in.
どれだけ多くの記憶を取り入れても
決して自我を見失わぬすべが
なるほど
I see.
吸血鬼から その方法を
教えてもらおうってわけか
So you want the vampires to tell you that method.
念のために聞くけど その方法が
人の身には無効だとしたら？
And let me ask just for the sake of it.
What if the method doesn't work on humans?
当然
禁書目録を人の身から外すまで
Obviously, I will move Index-Librorum-Prohibitorum away from a human's body.
その子を吸血鬼にするわけだ？
He wants to turn her into a vampire.
インデックスを？
Index?
He made espers use magic...
超能力者に魔術を使わせ…
...and is simply using Himegami...
姫神を利用するだけして…
...and in the end... he wants to turn Index into a vampire?!
なのに そのあげく
インデックスを吸血鬼にするだと？
Inevitably, it doesn't change the fact that Index-Librorum-Prohibitorum will be saved!
必然　それでも 禁書目録が
救われることに変わりはない
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
貴様にも それは分かるはずだ
You should understand that.
You, who have seen the "ending" that happens to her every exact one year period!
正しく１年ごとに巡り来る―
この子の最後を
見たであろう貴様には
At that time, she told me... that she didn't want to forget...
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
あのとき この子は告げたのだ
“決して忘れたくない”と
“教えを破り 死のうとも―”
...that she didn't want to die and go against her teachings...
...that she didn't want the memories in her heart to be erased...
“胸に抱えた思い出を
消したくない”と
指１本 動かせぬ体で
...she said all this with a body that couldn't even move a single finger!
この子は笑いながら告げたのだ！
She told me all this while she was smiling!!!
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
ハァ…
どうあっても
自分の考えは曲げない …か
You won't change your mind, no matter what, eh?
それなら…
Then, you tell him, current one!
ほら 言ってやれよ
今代のパートナー
Tell this alchemist that has a detrimental defect.
致命的な欠陥を抱えた
目の前の錬金術師に
お前 一体 いつの話をしてんだよ？
What year are you from, man?
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）なに？
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）そういうことさ
What?
That's how it is.
Index has been saved already.
インデックスは
とっくに救われてるんだ
君ではなく
ここにいる上条当麻によってね
Not by you, but by this Kamijyo Touma guy.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
君にはできなかったことを―
This guy accomplished what you couldn't.
こいつは
もう成し遂げてしまったんだよ
I'm sure you didn't hear the news because you betrayed
the Roman Catholic Church and hid yourself for three years.
ローマ正教を裏切り ３年間も
地下に潜っていた君には―
知る由もなかったろうがね
That...
そんなバカな…
ありえん 人の身で…
Impossible!
He's... a normal human...
not even a magician or alchemist...
それも 魔術師でもなければ―
錬金術師でもない人間に
一体 何ができるというのだ？
What can he possibly do?!
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
必要悪の教会(ネセサリウス)の…
Since this directly decreases the dignity of
the English Purist Church, I try not to spread this around.
イギリス清教の沽券(こけん)に関わるので
他言は控えるが
そうだねえ
こいつの右手は“幻想殺し(イマジンブレイカー)”という
But yeah...
This guy's right hand is called Imagine Breaker.
In other words, he possesses a power beyond what humans should.
つまり 人の身に余る能力の
持ち主ってわけだ
待て　ならば…
Wait, then...
Right, in other words, your efforts were completely in vain.
そう　君の努力は
全くの無駄骨だったってわけだ
だが 気にするな　インデックスは
君が望んだとおり…
But, hey, don't worry.
Index is, just like you desired,
extremely happy with her current partner.
今のパートナーと一緒にいて
とても幸せそうだよ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）当麻…
（姫神）うん？
Touma...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻…
Tou-ma...
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）アア…
（上条）インデックス！
Index!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
当麻…
Touma...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）おなか減った
（上条）アア…
I'm starving...
ウ～ン… リンゴ…
Apples...
（上条）アア…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）リンゴは…
Apples... from Aomori are...
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
フフッ… こいつはいい
This is a good one.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）倒れ伏せ 侵入者ども！
（上条・ｽﾃｲﾙ）ウッ！
On the ground, intruders!!!
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
我が思いを踏みにじり
我が辛苦をあざ笑い
You have trampled my emotions!
You have jeered at my hardships!
Very well, you will pay for my humiliation...
よかろう　この屈辱…
貴様らの死で あがなってもらう！
...with your deaths!!!
Don't!
（姫神）待って！
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）ハッ…
姫神… やめろ
Himegami.
Don't.
I understand your feelings.
（姫神）分かる 私 あなたの気持ち
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）ンッ…
He no longer...
そいつは もう…
（姫神）
でも 違う　今のあなたは…
But it's not right.
You're...
...needs you...
もう お前を…
I know, you're really...
知ってる 私　本当は…
The real you is...
本当のあなたは…
Die.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）死ね
（姫神）アア…
Himegami!!!
（上条）
姫神！
（姫神）
魔法が欲しかった
I yearned for magic.
私が呼び寄せた
I attracted them.
（母親）
ごめんね 秋沙ちゃん
Forgive me, Aisa-chan.
Forgive me!
ごめんね　アア…
（姫神）
そして みんな…
And everyone...
And everyone died in front of me...
みんな 私の前で
また殺したのね
I killed... again...
これ以上
誰も傷つけたくなかったから
I didn't want to hurt anyone anymore.
（姫神）
本当に…
本当に この血で誰かを救えるの？
Will my blood really save someone?
Will no one get hurt anymore?
本当に
もう誰も傷つけなくて済むの？
そのほほえみには
これっぽっちのウソも…
His smile didn't contain a single speck of lie.
あるのは たったひとつの願い
愛する人を救いたいという
It only contained one pure wish.
To save a loved one.
だから 私は…
That's why... I...
（受け止める音）
（上条）姫神！
Himegami!
ハハハハッ…
吸血殺し(ディープブラッド)など もはや無用
I do not need Deep Blood anymore.
Calmly, I have kept my promise.
悠然　約束は守った
これで その女も―
Now this woman has been released from the curse of her own blood.
おのが血の因果から
解き放たれたであろう
ハァ…
なっ… 我が黄金錬成(アルス＝マグナ)を
打ち消しただと？
H-He dispelled my Ars Magna?!
Impossible.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
ありえん
確かに姫神秋沙の死は確定した
Himegami Aisa's death was a certainty already!
その右手
聖域の秘術でも内包するか！
Is that right hand enchanted with
a secret power from the Sanctuary or what?!
ゴチャゴチャうっせえ
Shut the hell up already.
Who cares about that?!
…んなこた
もう どうだっていいんだよ
いいぜ
All right, man...
てめえが
何でも思いどおりに―
If you think you can do anything you want...
できるってんなら…
まずは その
ふざけた幻想をぶち殺す
...let me destroy that messed up illusion first!!!
ハァ… 床 冷てえ
This floor is cold...
（刺す音）
窒息死
Suffocate.
Die from electric shock.
感電死
（スパーク音）
Be crushed.
圧殺
I can dispel his attacks with my right hand.
ヤツの攻撃は 右手で消せる
I see.
なるほど　真説 その右手
Truly, your right hand can dispel even my Ars Magna without exception.
私の黄金錬成(アルス＝マグナ)も
例に漏れず 打ち消すらしい
That would mean you cannot dispel an attack that your right hand cannot touch.
ならばこそ
右手で触れられぬ攻撃なら―
打ち消すことは不可能なのだな？
（刺す音）
銃をこの手に
Bring a pistol into my hand.
弾丸は魔弾　用途は射出
Load with magic bullets.
Usage is shooting.
Number of rounds is twelve.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）数は１つで 十二分
（上条）ハッ…
Begin firing at a speed that exceeds human motion recognition!
人間の動体視力を超える速度にて
射出を開始せよ！
（銃声）
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
フッ… 簡単には殺さん
もう少し私を楽しませろ
I won't kill you easily.
Entertain me a bit more.
Mass produce the previous process,
simultaneous firing using the ten-hidden rifle!
先の手順を量産
10の暗器銃にて 同時射出！
ハハハハッ… 言ったろう
I told you, I won't kill you easily.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）簡単には殺さんとな
（上条）くそ…
Damn you.
（上条）ハッ…
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）準備は万端
Preparations are complete.
Simultaneous firing using the ten-hidden rifle-
10の暗器銃 同時射出を…
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
フン… 何だ？　それは
What kind of joke is that?
本当に 言葉ひとつで 現実を
ゆがめているみたいじゃないか
You seem like you really can distort reality with your words.
Obviously, Ars Magna is the pinnacle of all alchemy.
当然　黄金錬成(アルス＝マグナ)は錬金術の到達点
The world is now-
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）今や 世界は…
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）だったら…
Then, why did you need Deep Blood?
なぜ吸血殺し(ディープブラッド)を必要とした？
Why did you need to lure in vampires?
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
なぜ
吸血鬼を呼び寄せる必要がある？
Just create a vampire, I'm sure you can.
作ればいいじゃないか
吸血鬼くらい
Your words will do your bidding.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）言葉ひとつで命じるままに
（上条）ハッ…
Do tell, alchemist.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
なぜだ？　錬金術師
Why couldn't you create a vampire with your Ars Magna?
なぜ黄金錬成(アルス＝マグナ)とやらで
吸血鬼を作らなかった？
Wait, even before that, you needn't take such a long detour and-
いや それ以前に
そんな遠回りをしなくても…
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
宙を舞え！　ロンドンの神父！
Float in the sky, Father from London!!!
Stiyl!
（上条）ステイル！
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）全てを―
If you can distort everything just as your words command...
言葉のままに
ゆがめられるのなら…
Shred into pieces, rune magician!
はじけよ！　ルーンの魔術師！
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
フン…
Right, this guy's objective was...
そうだ　こいつの目的は…
If he could distort everything just as his words command...
全てを言葉のままに
ゆがめられるのなら…
...then why didn't he order for Index to be saved?
なんで こいつは インデックスの
救いを命じなかった？
Enough of this.
興がそがれた　射撃を中止
Halt firing.
He didn't think of it?
思えなかった？　救えるなんて
That she could be saved?
Change body to a slashing blade!
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
刀身による斬撃に変更
That's why he couldn't say it out loud?
だから 口にできなかった？
Well then...
さて 貴様の自信の源は
その得体(えたい)の知れぬ右手だったな？
The source of your confidence comes from your mysterious right hand, right?
That's how it is...
そういうことか
Then I shall slice off your right hand to start.
ならば まずは
その右手を切断することにしよう
This guy's power isn't one that distorts reality through his words.
こいつの力は 言葉のままに現実を
ゆがめることなんかじゃなくて…
Hidden rifle, rotate-fire your blade!
暗器銃 その刀身を回転射出せよ！
ハッ… な… なに？
W-What?
Wh-What...
な… 何だ？
What is wrong... with this guy?
何だ？　こいつは
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
あ… 暗器銃　先の手順を複製！
Hidden rifle, repeat the previous process!
Fire your blade to slice off the prey's head!
獲物の首を切断するために
その刀身を射出せよ！
ハッ… て… 手順を量産
10の刀身を一斉射出！
Reproduce process in mass!
Simultaneously fire all blades from ten-hidden rifle!
だ… 弾頭の刃を無数に配置
速やかに その体を解体せよ！
Deploy infinite amount of guillotine blades and quickly dismantle his body!
I-Impossible!
バ… バカな
A normal human that's not even a magician... is this...
魔術師でもない ただの人間に
こんな…
Hey, alchemist.
（上条）おい 錬金術師
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）ハッ…
You didn't think that you could get rid of my Imagine Breaker like this, did'ya?
てめえ まさか この程度で―
俺の幻想殺し(イマジンブレイカー)をつぶせるとか
思ってんじゃねえだろうな？
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
ヒイッ！
Can't even fight back without that, eh?
（上条）
そいつがなけりゃ
ハイにもなれねえな
Can't clear your head of useless thoughts without that, eh?
雑念をかき消せねえよな
What's the matter?
どうした？　言葉にしてみろよ
Go ahead and say it.
Don't... Don't come near me!
く… 来るな！
Come on, distort me with your words.
言葉のままに ゆがめてみろよ
Don't! Don't come near me!!!
く… 来るなーっ！
Impossible.
ありえん　我が黄金錬成(アルス＝マグナ)が
その効力を失うなど
My Ars Magna has lost its power...
ハッ… 待て　考えるな
そんなことを考えては…
Wait, don't think that!
If I think that way, then-
Stop.
やめろ　考えるな　信じろ
Stop thinking.
With my power, I won't lose to these people...
私の力をもってすれば
こんなヤツらには…
There's no way you can beat us.
（上条）かないっこねえよな
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）ハッ…
Because your power isn't one that distorts reality with your words...
（上条）
なぜなら てめえの能力は―
言葉のままに
現実をゆがめることじゃなくて…
This guy is a mons-
こいつ バケモ…
...but one that turns your thoughts into reality!
考えたことをそのまま
現実にしちまう力なんだからな！
I'm surprised it got reconnected successfully.
（ｶｴﾙ医師）
よく くっついたもんだね
Is your body a piece of fantasy?
（ｶｴﾙ医師）
君の体って 意外とファンタジー？
Doc, you're the one who did the surgery.
…ていうか
くっつけたの 先生でしょう
You've been hospitalized twice in ten days.
10日のうちに
２度も入院してくるなんて
Don't tell me you have a nurse fetish?
もしかして ナース属性？
What are you talking about?
何ですか？　それ
Would I slice off my hand just for that?
そんなもんのために
わざわざ 腕切りますか？
Pity, I thought I'd finally found a compatriot.
なんだ　同好の士じゃないのか
How boring.
（ｶｴﾙ医師）つまらん
（上条）おい
Hey!
Don't tell me he became a doctor for the nurses...
まさか ナース目当てで
医者になったとかじゃ…
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
うん… 見かけによらず
名医なんだな あの医者
That doctor is a pretty good one, unlike what his face suggests.
I guess.
まあな
I don't intend on befriending you, okay?
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
別に なれ合うつもりも
ないんだがね
I came to take a look at how you're doing.
一応 様子を見に来てやったよ
I... see...
ああ… そう
What's the matter?
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
どうした？
あの竜か？
That dragon?
That must be the form of despair that Aureolus felt at the eleventh hour.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
あれが 土壇場のアウレオルスが
感じた絶望の形だったんだろうね
What happened to Aureolus?
アウレオルスは どうなったんだ？
He lost all of his memories and his ability to use magic.
全ての記憶を失った
魔術を使う能力も
Killing him would kind of make us feel guilty,
とどめを刺すのも寝覚めが悪いし
顔形を変えて 野に放ってやったさ
so we changed his face, his form,
and released him back into the wild.
It was quite tough to do this behind the Thirteen Knights' back.
十三騎士団の目を盗むのには
少々 てこずったがね
そうか
I see.
Misawa Cram School has been closed down, as well.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
三沢塾も
閉鎖されることになったそうだ
I did think about thanking you,
一応 礼を言うつもりだったが
なんだか ばかばかしいんだよね
but it felt kind of stupid.
In the end, all you did was have Aureolus self-destruct.
君がやったことって―
結局は アウレオルスを
自滅させただけなんだから
フン… この上条当麻の
ステキ演技力に感謝するこった
You have to thank this Kamijyo Touma's Oscar-winning performance then.
I suppressed the pain of getting my hand sliced off...
なんつったって―
腕１本 ぶった斬られた痛みに
耐えながら―
ヤツを震え上がらせるに十分な
ハッタリをかましたんだからな
...and pulled off a rather big load of crap that made him piss in his pants.
Your senses were just paralyzed from the intense pain.
激痛に
感覚がマヒしていたんだろうさ
You got high from the shock.
ショックでハイになっていたとかね
Just like how Aureolus used those needles.
アウレオルスが
針を使って そうしていたように
あんな野郎と一緒にすんじゃねえ
Don't compare me to him!
Trying to save a girl by acquiring some weird magic...
女の子１人 救うとか言って
おかしな魔術を身につけて…
Putting all his desires... on vampires that we don't even know exist or not...
いるのかどうかも
分からない吸血鬼なんかに…
望みを…
Her partner from three years ago, huh?
（上条）
３年前のパートナーか…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）当麻！
（上条）あっ…
Touma~
Touma!
当麻！
Touma, I heard about it.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）当麻 聞いたよ
（上条）えっ なに？
What?
今回は
秋沙のために戦ったんだって？
You fought for Aisa's sake this time?
Aisa? Ahh, that wave-emitting fake magician...
秋沙？
ああ あの電波系エセ魔法使いね
Huh, wait, who told you about that?
…て お前 それ 誰に聞いたんだよ
Taf obfiouf.
決まってるんだよ
I do not emit... waves...
電波 …じゃない
Hi-Himegami?!
ひ… 姫神？
Wh-Why are you here with Index?!
な… なんで
インデックスとお前が ここに…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
別に 一緒に お見舞いに
来たかったわけじゃないんだよ
It's not like I wanted to come visit you with her.
But Aisa wanted to thank you no matter what.
ただ どうしても
秋沙が お礼をしたいって言うから
Why...
（姫神）どうして…
（上条）うん？
Why did you save me...
どうして私を…
どうして私のために…
Why did you do it for me...
We only met once in a fast food restaurant.
たった１度 ファストフードの
お店で会っただけなのに
I don't need a reason to save someone.
助けるのに
理由なんて要らねえだろう
Fay, Tofuma...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）それでね 当麻
（上条）食いながら しゃべんな
Don't speak while you're chewing.
…ていうか
いいかげん そこから下りろ
Heck, get off of me already.
You know!
あのね いろいろ話した結果 秋沙は
教会で預かることになったみたい
After much debate, the Church will be taking care of Aisa.
The Church?
教会？
おい まさか “歩く教会”も
教会なんですよってオチじゃ…
Don't tell me it's your Walking Church "Church" that's "taking in" again.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
あっ スフィンクス どこ行くの？
Sphinx, where are you going?
（上条）
病院に 猫連れてくんな！
Don't bring a cat to the hospital!
That's why I told her to leave the cat back at home.
だから あの部屋に
置いてきたほうがいいって―
言ったのに
（上条）何だ？ その―
Why does it sound like you've already moved in?!
既に 人ん家(ち)に上がり込んだことが
あるみたいなセリフは
Wait! Wait for me, Sphinx!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
待って！
ちょっと待ってよ スフィンクス！
PLACEHOLDER
Don't run around in a hospital room!
病室で暴れんじゃねえ！
PLACEHOLDER
You can't scratch the wall!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
あっ！　壁ひっかいちゃダメだよ
What are you doing?!
（上条）
何やってんだよ…
Ah... the wall's...
（上条）
ああ 壁が…
ああ もう！　不幸だ！
Ah... damn...
～♪
SUCH MISFORTUNE!!!
Next Episode
Misaka's identical sister who appeared before me.
（上条）
俺の前に現れた御坂(みさか)と瓜二(うりふた)つの妹
Seems like she's got a problem.
And the white-haired guy that is chasing her.
なんだか ワケありらしいのだが
そして 彼女を追う白髪の少年
Eh? The strongest, Level 5 of Academy City?
えっ？　学園最強のレベル５(ファイブ)？
Next time, "Misaka Mikoto".
次回 「お姉様(みさかみこと)」
When science and magic cross paths,
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる
this epic will begin!